<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="headlines.xsl"?>
<headlines>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Quake Researchers 'Look' Deep Inside Fault With Cold War-era Gravity Sensor]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040908090300.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Using classified technology developed by the military during the Cold War, a team of geoscientists led by Rice University's Manik Talwani is conducting a first-of-its-kind experiment on California's famed San Andreas fault this week.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Scientists Discover Way To Slow The Progression Of Prostate Cancer]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040908081541.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A UK based team of scientists and doctors have found a way to slow the development and spread of prostate cancer by stopping certain genes from becoming active.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[New Research Suggests Link Between Maternal Diet And Childhood Leukemia Risk]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040909074410.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A new study suggests that eating more vegetables, fruit and protein before pregnancy may lower the risk of having a child who develops leukemia, the most common childhood cancer in the United States.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[NASA Gravity Probe B Mission Enters Science Phase, Ready To Test Einstein's Theory]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040908091101.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Gravity Probe B, a NASA spacecraft to test two predictions of Albert Einstein's general theory of relativity, achieved a major milestone last week with the completion of the first phase of its mission and the transition into the science phase. The GP-B mission is now one step closer to shedding new light on the fundamental properties of our universe.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA['Unsung Species' Ignored On Endangered List]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910082907.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[The global extinction crisis ignores thousands of affiliated species that are also at risk of being wiped out, making the list of endangered species much larger and more serious than originally thought, says a study produced in part at the University of Alberta.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>1</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Sandia Helps Navy In Shaping Future Of Aircraft Carrier Operations]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040909075400.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Researchers at the National Nuclear Security Administration's Sandia National Laboratories are helping the U.S. Navy create the next generation of aircraft carriers by reviewing and analyzing current Carrier Air Wing flight operations, maintenance, and support functions.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Spontaneous Mutation Produces New MAO A/B Knockout Mouse]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910075119.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A combination of luck and scientific curiosity has produced a mouse lacking two isoenzymes, MAO A and MAO B, that have been linked to violent criminal behavior and Parkinson's disease. The MAO A/B knockout mouse should provide an excellent model in which to address the specific roles of these neurotransmitters and their receptors in anxiety and stress-related disorders.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Researchers Discover Why Mutant Gene Causes Colon Cancer]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910075443.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Mutations in the adenomatous polyposis coli (APC) tumor suppressor gene have been found to cause 85 percent of colon cancers. Now researchers at the University of Utah's Huntsman Cancer Institute know why.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Genesis Team Begins Inventory Of Science Canister]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910081347.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Genesis team specialists are beginning the process of conducting inventory of the contents of the craft's science canister.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Engineers Model Effects Of Hurricane Force Winds On Structures]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910080622.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[As the rains from the downgraded Hurricane Frances move northward while the eastern U.S. continues to watch Hurricane Ivan's approach, the destruction from the heavy winds and rains is mounting into the billions of dollars. In most cases, low-rise buildings, including residential, institutional, and commercial structures are the most vulnerable and carry the brunt of the damage and losses from extreme wind.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[NASA's Grace Gravity Mission Weighs In On Earth's Changing Climate]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910081519.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[For the first time, scientists have demonstrated that precise measurements of Earth's changing gravity field can effectively monitor changes in the planet's climate and weather.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Left And Right Ears Not Created Equal As Newborns Process Sound, Finds UCLA/UA Research]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910082553.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Challenging decades of scientific belief that the decoding of sound originates from a preferred side of the brain, UCLA and University of Arizona scientists have demonstrated that right-left differences for the auditory processing of sound start at the ear.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Disruption Of Protein-folding Causes Neurodegeneration, Mental Retardation]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910075608.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Excess accumulation in brain cells of a fat molecule called GM1-ganglioside (GM1) disrupts the folding of newly assembled proteins into their proper shapes, triggering nerve degeneration and mental retardation in children.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Yale Scientists Bring Quantum Optics To A Microchip]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910081014.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A report in the journal Nature describes the first experiment in which a single photon is coherently coupled to a single superconducting qubit (quantum bit or "artificial atom").]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Nanotechnology Leads To Discovery Of Super Superconductors]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910080120.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[University of California scientists working at Los Alamos National Laboratory with a researcher from the University of Cambridge have demonstrated a simple and industrially scaleable method for improving the current densities of superconducting coated conductors in magnetic field environments.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Cassini Discovers Ring And One, Possibly Two, Objects At Saturn]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910081629.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Scientists examining Saturn's contorted F ring, which has baffled them since its discovery, have found one small body, possibly two, orbiting in the F ring region, and a ring of material associated with Saturn's moon Atlas.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[OutFoxed: New Research May Redefine Late-stage Cardiac Development]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910075310.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A team of University of Pennsylvania School of Medicine researchers, led by Edward E. Morrisey, PhD, Associate Professor of Medicine, have been investigating how the heart develops from its earliest stages of development to its late stages, with the hope of learning why some hearts don't develop correctly.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[The Search For A Kinder, Gentler Chemotherapy]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910080724.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Painful and damaging chemotherapy may one day be a thing of the past. Researchers at the Georgia Institute of Technology and Purdue University have developed nano-sized particles that can target and trick cancer cells into absorbing them. Once inside, the particles may soon be able to deliver a pharmaceutical payload, killing the tumor from within, avoiding the destruction of healthy cells responsible for much of the damage caused by traditional chemotherapy.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Serotonin Metabolites In Mollusks Suggest Pathways For Human Therapies]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910080324.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[From mollusks to mammals, newly discovered chemical pathways of serotonin in the nervous system are paving a path toward future pharmaceutical treatments for depression and other disorders.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Government Study Finds Nearly Half A Million Medical Device Injuries A Year]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040913091941.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[An estimated 454,383 people suffered injuries from medical devices ? ranging from wheelchair accidents to careless toothbrushing ? in one 12-month period from 1999-2000, say researchers from two federal regulatory agencies.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Bacteria Use 'Molecular Lasso' To Cop Copper]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040910082755.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[The bacteria that destroy about one-third of the potent greenhouse gas methane before it can reach the atmosphere use a neat trick to gather a key nutrient for the job. They produce a small organic compound and release it into the surrounding environment, where it "lassos" atoms of copper.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[New Dye Directly Reveals Activated Proteins In Living Cells]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040913090832.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A series of experiments reported on this week in the journal Science shows for the first time that novel biosensor dyes can directly reveal activation of proteins in individual living cells.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[The (Brain) Stuff Of Which Dreams Are Made]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040913092356.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[In a study published September 10, 2004, in the online edition of the Annals of Neurology, scientists describe a patient who lost all dreaming, and very little else, following a stroke in one distinct region of the brain, suggesting that this area is crucial for the generation of dreams.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230844936986</hlid>
      <guid>63230844936986</guid>
      <owner>63230844904459</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Genesis Scientists Bouncing Back From Hard Landing]]></title>
      <link>http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2004/09/040913092447.htm</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Scientists who conducted the preliminary assessment of the Genesis canister are encouraged by what they see. They believe it may be possible to achieve the most important portions of their science objectives.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:35:36+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.sciencedaily.com/images/logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845077769</hlid>
      <guid>63230845077769</guid>
      <owner>63230844971516</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Linux Clustering]]></title>
      <link>http://slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/13/1934248</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:37:57+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>1</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845077769</hlid>
      <guid>63230845077769</guid>
      <owner>63230844971516</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Linux Standard Base 2.0 released]]></title>
      <link>http://slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/13/1955251</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:37:57+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845077769</hlid>
      <guid>63230845077769</guid>
      <owner>63230844971516</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[New Worm Installs Sniffer]]></title>
      <link>http://slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/13/2024234</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:37:57+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845077769</hlid>
      <guid>63230845077769</guid>
      <owner>63230844971516</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Review of Yoper Linux v2.1]]></title>
      <link>http://slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/13/222228</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:37:57+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845077769</hlid>
      <guid>63230845077769</guid>
      <owner>63230844971516</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[AMD Desktops Outsell Intel]]></title>
      <link>http://slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/13/2241256</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:37:57+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>1</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845077769</hlid>
      <guid>63230845077769</guid>
      <owner>63230844971516</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Fedora Project Considering "Stateless Linux"]]></title>
      <link>http://slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/13/2318224</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:37:57+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>1</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845077769</hlid>
      <guid>63230845077769</guid>
      <owner>63230844971516</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Jetway PT800TWIN - Dual User Hardware]]></title>
      <link>http://slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/13/2345235</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:37:57+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845077769</hlid>
      <guid>63230845077769</guid>
      <owner>63230844971516</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Spam Turns 100, By One Reckoning]]></title>
      <link>http://slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/13/2230210</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:37:57+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845077769</hlid>
      <guid>63230845077769</guid>
      <owner>63230844971516</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Hot Rod Job For SpaceShipOne]]></title>
      <link>http://slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/13/2354207</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:37:57+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>1</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845077769</hlid>
      <guid>63230845077769</guid>
      <owner>63230844971516</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Obsessively Detailed Map Of Springfield]]></title>
      <link>http://slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/14/0247237</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:37:57+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>1</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845081474</hlid>
      <guid>http://www.wired.com/news/business/0,1367,64927,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</guid>
      <owner>63230845074173</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Idaho Hot Potato: Tech Companies]]></title>
      <link>http://www.wired.com/news/business/0,1367,64927,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A sparsely populated western state best known for potatoes is becoming a magnet for tech entrepreneurs. The slow pace, absence of traffic and low-rise landscape has helped lure 800 tech companies to the state.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-12T14:39:00+-8</date>
      <image>http://static.wired.com/news/images/netcenterb.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845081474</hlid>
      <guid>http://www.wired.com/news/business/0,1367,64898,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</guid>
      <owner>63230845074173</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[U.S. Exports DMCA Down Under]]></title>
      <link>http://www.wired.com/news/business/0,1367,64898,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Negotiations for a trade agreement between the U.S. and Australia are raising a ruckus among Aussie digital rights activists. At issue is a plan to enact a law there modeled on the controversial Digital Millennium Copyright Act. By Patrick Gray.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T02:00:00+-8</date>
      <image>http://static.wired.com/news/images/netcenterb.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845081474</hlid>
      <guid>http://www.wired.com/news/technology/0,1282,64902,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</guid>
      <owner>63230845074173</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Public Fiber Tough to Swallow]]></title>
      <link>http://www.wired.com/news/technology/0,1282,64902,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Cities that try to set up their own broadband networks are facing staunch opposition from cable and phone companies, who see publicly funded fiber-optic networks as a threat to their own bottom line. By John Gartner.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T02:00:00+-8</date>
      <image>http://static.wired.com/news/images/netcenterb.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845081474</hlid>
      <guid>http://www.wired.com/news/business/0,1367,64931,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</guid>
      <owner>63230845074173</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Sears Takes On Cyberspace]]></title>
      <link>http://www.wired.com/news/business/0,1367,64931,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</link>
      <body><![CDATA[The retailer begins selling apparel and home furnishings online. Also: IBM launches a new, cheaper line of servers.... Cisco plans a new line of low-end routers.... and more.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T08:50:00+-8</date>
      <image>http://static.wired.com/news/images/netcenterb.gif</image>
      <read>1</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845081474</hlid>
      <guid>http://www.wired.com/news/evote/0,2645,64938,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</guid>
      <owner>63230845074173</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Nevada's Seamless E-Vote]]></title>
      <link>http://www.wired.com/news/evote/0,2645,64938,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</link>
      <body><![CDATA[The success of last week's primary election using touch-screen voting machines heartens officials in other states, where e-voting has been problematic. Still, the Silver State may be in a unique situation.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T10:35:00+-8</date>
      <image>http://static.wired.com/news/images/netcenterb.gif</image>
      <read>1</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845081474</hlid>
      <guid>http://www.wired.com/news/medtech/0,1286,64916,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</guid>
      <owner>63230845074173</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Frozen Eggs Showing Promise]]></title>
      <link>http://www.wired.com/news/medtech/0,1286,64916,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Italian researchers have achieved 13 human births using previously frozen eggs. It's encouraging for women who want to preserve their fertility, but efficiency is still low. By Kristen Philipkoski.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T02:00:00+-8</date>
      <image>http://static.wired.com/news/images/netcenterb.gif</image>
      <read>1</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845081474</hlid>
      <guid>http://www.wired.com/news/technology/0,1282,64900,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</guid>
      <owner>63230845074173</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Study: Recycling Cost Overstated]]></title>
      <link>http://www.wired.com/news/technology/0,1282,64900,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Nova Scotia makes a name for itself as a rigorous enforcer of recycling. Now a study finds that while the province may be spending millions on its garbage program, it's actually saving far more. By Stephen Leahy.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T02:00:00+-8</date>
      <image>http://static.wired.com/news/images/netcenterb.gif</image>
      <read>1</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845081474</hlid>
      <guid>http://www.wired.com/news/technology/0,1282,64914,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</guid>
      <owner>63230845074173</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Step Toward Universal Computing]]></title>
      <link>http://www.wired.com/news/technology/0,1282,64914,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A Silicon Valley company claims to have developed a universal emulator that's uncharacteristically fast. For one thing, it could mean the latest games are immediately available for the Mac. By Leander Kahney.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T02:00:00+-8</date>
      <image>http://static.wired.com/news/images/netcenterb.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845081474</hlid>
      <guid>http://www.wired.com/news/privacy/0,1848,64911,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</guid>
      <owner>63230845074173</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Pentagon Revives Memory Project]]></title>
      <link>http://www.wired.com/news/privacy/0,1848,64911,00.html?tw=rss.TOP</link>
      <body><![CDATA[The Department of Defense is handing out contracts for a project to record what soldiers see and do in battle zones. The new initiative closely resembles another, called LifeLog, that the Pentagon scrapped months ago. By Noah Shachtman.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T02:00:00+-8</date>
      <image>http://static.wired.com/news/images/netcenterb.gif</image>
      <read>1</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845387324</hlid>
      <guid>63230845387324</guid>
      <owner>63230845133148</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Linux in Government: Technical Aspects of the Emergency Response Network System]]></title>
      <link>http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7738</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A conversation with one of the founders of YHD Software, the company supplying Emergency Response Network systems to the FBI and DHS.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:07+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.linuxjournal.com/images/logo_tiny.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845387324</hlid>
      <guid>63230845387324</guid>
      <owner>63230845133148</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Programming Tools: eric3]]></title>
      <link>http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7739</link>
      <body><![CDATA[The first article for this new monthly column looks at eric3, a GUI-based IDE for Python.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:07+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.linuxjournal.com/images/logo_tiny.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845387324</hlid>
      <guid>63230845387324</guid>
      <owner>63230845133148</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[XML <_specialsign_> DocBook: Structured Technical Documentation Authoring]]></title>
      <link>http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7740</link>
      <body><![CDATA[An introduction to XML and DocBook: what is it and why should I learn yet another data format?]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:07+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.linuxjournal.com/images/logo_tiny.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845387324</hlid>
      <guid>63230845387324</guid>
      <owner>63230845133148</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[The First Linux Installfest in Iraq]]></title>
      <link>http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7748</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Determined to surpass all the obstacles and embrace new technology, the Iraqi LUG held its first installfest.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:07+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.linuxjournal.com/images/logo_tiny.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845387324</hlid>
      <guid>63230845387324</guid>
      <owner>63230845133148</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Linux in Government: Will Schwarzenegger Terminate Windows?]]></title>
      <link>http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7750</link>
      <body><![CDATA[If he can see the predators hiding in the political jungle, he may.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:07+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.linuxjournal.com/images/logo_tiny.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845387324</hlid>
      <guid>63230845387324</guid>
      <owner>63230845133148</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[From the Editor -- October 2004: Security]]></title>
      <link>http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7673</link>
      <body><![CDATA[The security message is closing Linux migration deals. Now it's up to us to deliver the secure environment people want.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:07+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.linuxjournal.com/images/logo_tiny.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845387324</hlid>
      <guid>63230845387324</guid>
      <owner>63230845133148</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[OOo Off the Wall: The Outlining and the Ecstasy]]></title>
      <link>http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7759</link>
      <body><![CDATA[With a bit of practice and some of these tips, you can become an outlining pro, even if you haven't done an outline since Freshmen Comp.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:07+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.linuxjournal.com/images/logo_tiny.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845387324</hlid>
      <guid>63230845387324</guid>
      <owner>63230845133148</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[An Introduction to GraphViz]]></title>
      <link>http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7275</link>
      <body><![CDATA[How to use command-line tools and basic GraphViz utilities to produce graphs both simple and complex.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:07+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.linuxjournal.com/images/logo_tiny.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845387324</hlid>
      <guid>63230845387324</guid>
      <owner>63230845133148</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Linux in Government: Neglecting the Community, a Commentary]]></title>
      <link>http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7766</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Linux vendors get failing grades in Linux community relations.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:07+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.linuxjournal.com/images/logo_tiny.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845387324</hlid>
      <guid>63230845387324</guid>
      <owner>63230845133148</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Linux MIDI: a Brief History, Part 1]]></title>
      <link>http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7773</link>
      <body><![CDATA[An overview of the creation and evolution of MIDI, from early standalone equipment to an all-in-one computerized composition environment.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:07+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.linuxjournal.com/images/logo_tiny.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[This Week on Perl 6, Week Ending 2004-06-27]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/07/p6pdigest/20040702.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Getting ready for the Piethon is a major concern, while the language list deals with various ways of modifying and annotating expressions.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[This Week on Perl 6, Week Ending 2004-07-04]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/07/p6pdigest/20040704.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Work begins on a Perl 6 regexp parser, and Unicode manipulation of strings prompts discussion on the language list.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Autopilots in Perl]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/07/09/xplane.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Jeffrey Goff explains how to connect the X-Plane flight simulator with a Perl console to build new instrument panels, traffic simulators, and even an autopilot in Perl.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Accessible Software]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/07/14/accessibility.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Jouke Visser demonstrates how to adapt your Perl programs for use by those who have difficulty using a mouse or keyboard.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[This Week on Perl 6, Week Ending 2004-07-18]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/07/p6pdigest/20040718.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[The Piethon benchmark contest is beginning to loom, and the language list discusses how scalars should be interpolated and subscripted.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Building Applications with POE]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/07/22/poe.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[In Matt Cashner's second article on POE, he describes how to fit together POE's components into event-driven applications.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Giving Lightning Talks]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/07/30/lightningtalk.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[It's conference season, and there's still a chance to sign up for lightning talks. Until now, there were no written rules for giving lighting talks. Mark Fowler explains.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[This Week on Perl 6, Week Ending 2004-07-31]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/07/p6pdigest/20040731.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[The pie hits! --more--]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Perl Command-Line Options]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/08/09/commandline.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[After looking at special variables, Dave Cross now casts his eye over the impressive range of functionality available from simple command-line options to the Perl interpreter.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[The State of the Onion]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/08/18/onion.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Larry Wall's eighth annual State of the Onion address from OSCON 2004 related screensavers to surgery to Perl and the community.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[This Week on Perl 6, Week Ending 2004-08-20]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/08/p6pdigest/20040820.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Better register spilling, COBOL on Parrot, and a re-examination of lookahead from Apocalypse 12. All this and more in the latest Perl 6 summary.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Content Management with Bricolage]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/08/27/bricolage.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[David Wheeler presents an introduction to the Bricolage content management system (CMS).]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Hacking Perl in Nightclubs]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/08/31/livecode.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[By editing Perl programs on-the-fly, in real-time, Alex Mclean is producing some really interesting computer music. He talks to perl.com about how it all works.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[This Week on Perl 6, Week Ending 2004-09-03]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/09/p6pdigest/20040903.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Piers Cawley has the latest from the Perl 6 mailing lists. The Parrot folks create some TODOs, hash out math semantics, and discuss cross-compiling. The Perl 6 language folks argue about ranges, roles, pipelines, and PRE and POST hooks.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845390719</hlid>
      <guid>63230845390719</guid>
      <owner>63230845155380</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Lightning Articles]]></title>
      <link>http://www.perl.com/pub/a/2004/09/09/lightning.html</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Got something to say about Perl, but don't want to stretch it out to a full perl.com article? In the tradition of lightning talks, we now present lightning articles!]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:10+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845396627</hlid>
      <guid>63230845396627</guid>
      <owner>63230845167628</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Audacity sound editor 1.2.2]]></title>
      <link>http://sourceforge.net/forum/forum.php?forum_id=402501</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Audacity is a multi-track audio editor and recorder for Linux, Windows, and Mac OS X.  You can use Audacity to play and record sounds, apply effects such as Change Pitch and Change Tempo, and quickly edit large recordings with unlimited undo.

Audacity 1.2.2 is a new stable version of the free Audacity sound editor.  This version features major bug fixes and new features such as VU meters for monitoring playback and recording levels.

You can find this latest release here:

https://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=6235&package_id=6294
]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:16+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845396627</hlid>
      <guid>63230845396627</guid>
      <owner>63230845167628</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Gallery 1.4.4-pl2 is now Available!]]></title>
      <link>http://sourceforge.net/forum/forum.php?forum_id=402497</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Gallery is a slick, intuitive web based photo gallery with authenticated users and privileged albums. Easy to install, configure and use. Photo management includes automatic thumbnails, resizing, rotation, etc. User privileges make this great for communities.

Gallery 1.4.4-pl2 is an update to Gallery 1.4.4-pl1 that addresses two issues discovered after the release. Skins will now work properly in all situations and extra long filenames for uploaded files are now handled properly. 

Download 1.4.4-pl1 from http://sf.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=7130

Visit http://gallery.sourceforge.net/article.php?sid=135 for more details.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:16+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845396627</hlid>
      <guid>63230845396627</guid>
      <owner>63230845167628</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Crystal Space 0.98r004 released]]></title>
      <link>http://sourceforge.net/forum/forum.php?forum_id=404903</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Here is a new release of Crystal Space 0.98r004. Crystal Space is an Open Source and feature rich 3D Engine which runs on Linux, Windows, and MacOS/X.



Lots has changed since 0.96 (see http://sourceforge.net/project/shownotes.php?group_id=649&release_id=266198). This is the fourth release of 0.98. This version should now be very stable. Go to http://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=649&package_id=664&release_id=266198 to download Crystal Space.


Greetings,]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:16+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845396627</hlid>
      <guid>63230845396627</guid>
      <owner>63230845167628</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[GanttProject 1.10 released]]></title>
      <link>http://sourceforge.net/forum/forum.php?forum_id=405040</link>
      <body><![CDATA[GanttProject version 1.10 is available. New features include export to new formats (XFig, CSV), management of role sets (now it is possible to define application-level roles and share them in different projects). UI improvements (new plastic theme, multiselection), WebDAV bugfixes. Ganttproject lets you plan projects using a Gantt chart. It is written in Java. GanttProject use a XML file format. It can export the project in HTML Web pages or PDF document (using XSLT) or image files. It support 21 languages.



See changelog for details.]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:16+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845396627</hlid>
      <guid>63230845396627</guid>
      <owner>63230845167628</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[phpMyAdmin 2.6.0-rc2 is released]]></title>
      <link>http://sourceforge.net/forum/forum.php?forum_id=404839</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Here is the second release candidate for version 2.6.0. Thinks are going well, version 2.6.0-rc1 was tested a lot (with more than 45700 downloads). phpMyAdmin is a tool written in PHP intended to handle the administration of MySQL over the Web. Currently it can create and drop databases, create/drop/alter tables, delete/edit/add fields, execute any SQL statement, manage keys on fields.

]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:16+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845396627</hlid>
      <guid>63230845396627</guid>
      <owner>63230845167628</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Xaraya 0.9.10 released]]></title>
      <link>http://sourceforge.net/forum/forum.php?forum_id=404582</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Xaraya is extensible, open source software written in PHP and licensed under the GNU General Public License. Xaraya utilizes robust permissions, data management and multilingual systems to dynamically integrate and manage content. We are pleased to announce the release of Xaraya 0.9.10 Beta. It is an exciting time in Xaraya development with the pace quickening as we approach Version 1.0. In this 0.9.10 Beta release we see further consolidation and stabilization of the code base and much enhanced functionality. There is also a move towards a concentration on performance and usability enhancements which are evident in the feature list for this release. Congratulations and thanks to all those who have contributed. I'd also like to thank our users who have been providing invaluable feedback and bug reporting during our journey towards Version 1.0. Your continued support in this area will ensure Xaraya maintains its place as a leader in Web Application Framework development and innovation.


Read on for more details of the release ...

General enhancements:
- Reduced dependencies between subsystems
- New import and export tools to ease both site migration, and the movement of specific data to and from Xaraya
- Code rework and tidying for improved performance, security and ease in moving to PHP5

Performance and Security enhancements
- Implementation of binding variables for database calls throughout the codebase
- Improved cache management for module, block and pages, and introduction of query caching
- New Xaraya sessionless caching for anonymous site users
- Faster security checks

Internationalization
- Additional language support for core and modules with Xaraya now translated into over 20 languages
- Numerous improvements to the Xaraya installer, in particular default installer support for 8 languages
- Translations functionality for themes in addition to previous module support
- New configurability and translation of module names

General Module and Usability enhancements
- A number of WYSIWYG editors providing a choice in functionality,including formatting using classes in a CSS style sheet of your choice
- Navigation enhancements in the Roles and Privileges modules providing easier management
- Added functionality so Roles names can be reused, with recall and purge functions for deleted roles
- Templates for Mail and Roles email messages allowing fully customizable email messaging
- Improved notification and subscription services through enhanced Mail and PubSub functionality
- Enhancements to the logging subsystem allowing the Site Admin to configure the logger
- Improved events handler
- New dynamicdata properties, additions without core file editing, and enhancements to existing properties
- Many enhanced features in other favourites such as Xarbb and Articles

Blocklayout and Templates
- Improvements to the Blocklayout compiler and enhanced functionality
- Large scale cleanup of templates and improved code
- Improved standards compliancy for XHTML 1.0 Strict
- Enhancements to custom BlockLayout tags

.. and of course many bugfixes to the previous version.

Visit:  http://www.xaraya.com
Download: http://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=64578
Language Packs: http://xaraya.com/downloads/languages
Discuss: news://news.xaraya.com
Chat: irc://irc.xaraya.com
Forums: http://www.xaraya.com/index.php/xarbb]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:16+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845396627</hlid>
      <guid>63230845396627</guid>
      <owner>63230845167628</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Bygfoot 1.6.1 and 1.7.1 available]]></title>
      <link>http://sourceforge.net/forum/forum.php?forum_id=405738</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Bygfoot is a small and simple graphical football (a.k.a. soccer) manager game featuring many internat. leagues & cups. You manage a team from one such league: you form the team, buy & sell players, get promoted or relegated and of course try to be successful.

The new releases correct an extremely annoying bug that caused the game to hang. There's also an online update script in the source packages that helps you keep your Bygfoot version up-to-date without downloading new packages manually.

You can find a copy of these releases for download here:

https://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=46139]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:16+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845396627</hlid>
      <guid>63230845396627</guid>
      <owner>63230845167628</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[chroot_safe 1.2 released]]></title>
      <link>http://sourceforge.net/forum/forum.php?forum_id=405757</link>
      <body><![CDATA[chroot_safe 1.2 released

chroot_safe is a small tool replacing chroot and friends, allowing you to chroot almost any application in a sane and safe manner.

version 1.2 is an update to increase portability. The software is now verified on Solaris on addition to Linux and FreeBSD and is expected to run on mostly any UNIX like system with LD_PRELOAD support.

You can find this latest release here:

https://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=110671&package_id=119556]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:16+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845396627</hlid>
      <guid>63230845396627</guid>
      <owner>63230845167628</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[ACal 2.2.2 Released]]></title>
      <link>http://sourceforge.net/forum/forum.php?forum_id=405999</link>
      <body><![CDATA[ACal is a web based event calendar that does not require a database server. It is made to be easy to install and to be able to run on just about any typical ISP's server with PHP installed.

ACal 2.2.2 was released to fix two bugs. First of all a bug when clicking on single digit days in the month view to get into the day view and second, a bug where after installing you can login with a blank username and password. More details in the release notes.

You can find this latest release here:

https://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=105617&package_id=113878]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:16+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845396627</hlid>
      <guid>63230845396627</guid>
      <owner>63230845167628</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Compiere Release 2.5.1f]]></title>
      <link>http://sourceforge.net/forum/forum.php?forum_id=406147</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Smart ERP+CRM solution for Small-Medium Enterprises in the global marketplace covering all areas from customer management, supply chain and accounting. For $2-200M revenue companies looking for "brick and click" first tier functionality.

Compiere released its newest Production Release 2.5.1f !

The emphasis of this release was the improved Server infrastructure.  You can now monitor the (accounting, request, workflow, alert) processors and their logs from the web. The default URL is http://localhost/compiereMonitor
and requires to log on with a user id with System Administrator role.

New are also Alerts - you define the situation you want to be alerted of and Compiere will send an email with details, if the conditions are met.

Document Value based Workflows allow you to start a workflow automatically, if a certain condition is met in any Entity in the system.
You can use this for example to do a credit check for new Business Partners or when the address was changed.  Together with the Document Process Workflows and Alerts, you can now model all Business Processes.

Due to Server Infrastructure changes, you need to
- Delete the jboss sub-directory Before upgrading (extracting the zip/gz)
- After upgrading, you need to define Accounting and Request Processors for your clients. They are created automatically if you create a new client, but not for existing ones.

If you have a translated system, you should run "Synchronize Terminology" after migration or after importing the translation.


The Toronto training was quickly fully booked.  Note that the next intensive training "from the source" is December 6-10 in Miami, FL ... and book early if you want to guarantee your seat.

You can find the latest release here:

https://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=29057
]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:16+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Pegasus Mobile NoteTaker]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/13/review_notetaker/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[<strong>Review</strong> Neat idea - shame about the price?]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T12:41:05+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[MP fingers O2 in overcharging rumpus]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/13/mp_o2/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Calls on users to check their bills]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T14:26:50+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Why did Sendo bury the hatchet with MS?]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/13/sendo_microsoft_hatchet/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[<strong>Analysis</strong> Too expensive to bury it <em>in</em> MS?]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T15:01:06+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Scientists ponder sluggish Pioneers]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/13/gravity_tank_leak/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Is gravity wrong, or is it a leaky tank?]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T17:10:23+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Beware of malformed MIME artists]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/13/mime_vuln/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Content checking bypass ploy]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T17:16:32+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[IBM does Linux-only dance on Power]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/13/ibm_linuxonly_powerbox/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Think not of AIX]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T18:13:26+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[MS anti-spam proposal returned to sender]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/13/ietf_bounces_sender_id/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[IETF endorses patent fears]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T18:25:00+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[New P2P software could end illegal music squabbles]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/13/grouper_p2p_launc/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Catch a Grouper]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-13T19:24:56+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[CA upgrades BrightStor line with gusto]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/14/ca_brightstor_refresh/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[An integration paradise]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T00:32:37+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[EC waves through HP Synstar deal]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/14/ec_approves_hp_synstar/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[<strong>Brief</strong> Insignificant]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T07:18:01+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[GPRS prices drop 40%]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/14/gprs_mobile_data/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[More bangs per buck but still pricey]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T08:37:20+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Freedom of Information means grief for small biz]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/14/smallbiz_freedom_info/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[What price freedom?]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T09:06:32+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[MS Virtual Server hits the streets]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/14/virtual_server_2005/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[VMWare rival]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T09:11:39+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Poker-faced BOFH plays jokers wild]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/14/bofh_2004_episode_30/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[<strong>Episode 30</strong> Upping the ante]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T09:18:52+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845398039</hlid>
      <guid>63230845398039</guid>
      <owner>63230845178183</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Apple vs Apple: 'mind boggling' pay-out imminent - report]]></title>
      <link>http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/14/apple_vs_apple/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[And that's just the lawyers' fees...]]></body>
      <date>2004-09-14T09:29:00+0</date>
      <image>http://www.theregister.co.uk/Design/graphics/Reg_default/The_Register_RSS.png</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845399351</hlid>
      <guid>63230845399351</guid>
      <owner>63230845189239</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Cooking for Engineers]]></title>
      <link>http://developers.slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/10/1734235</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:19+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845399351</hlid>
      <guid>63230845399351</guid>
      <owner>63230845189239</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[KDE Gets Gecko/Mozilla Support]]></title>
      <link>http://developers.slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/11/2119249</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:19+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845399351</hlid>
      <guid>63230845399351</guid>
      <owner>63230845189239</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[RMS On How To Fight Software Patents]]></title>
      <link>http://developers.slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/11/238230</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:19+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845399351</hlid>
      <guid>63230845399351</guid>
      <owner>63230845189239</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Firefox 1.0 Preview Release Candidates Available]]></title>
      <link>http://developers.slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/12/1211230</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:19+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845399351</hlid>
      <guid>63230845399351</guid>
      <owner>63230845189239</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[2004 ICFP Contest Spinoff Game]]></title>
      <link>http://developers.slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/12/1450257</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:19+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845399351</hlid>
      <guid>63230845399351</guid>
      <owner>63230845189239</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Mountain Biking Helps Squash Bugs]]></title>
      <link>http://developers.slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/12/1741248</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:19+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845399351</hlid>
      <guid>63230845399351</guid>
      <owner>63230845189239</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[.Net On Lego Mindstorm]]></title>
      <link>http://developers.slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/12/1918221</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:19+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845399351</hlid>
      <guid>63230845399351</guid>
      <owner>63230845189239</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[IBM to Open Voice Recognition Software]]></title>
      <link>http://developers.slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/13/1058241</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:19+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845399351</hlid>
      <guid>63230845399351</guid>
      <owner>63230845189239</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[JRuby Great Addition To Java Development]]></title>
      <link>http://developers.slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/13/1438225</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:19+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845399351</hlid>
      <guid>63230845399351</guid>
      <owner>63230845189239</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Independent Developers Fight Piracy <_specialsign_> Lose]]></title>
      <link>http://developers.slashdot.org/article.pl?sid=04/09/13/1357202</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:19+01:00</date>
      <image>http://images.slashdot.org/topics/topicslashdot.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Caffeine: Black Black Gum/Candy]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/caffeine/candy/68ad/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Computing: Web Designer's Mousepads]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/computing/accessories/5b15/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Cube Goodies: R/C Hovercraft]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/cubegoodies/toys/5ef3/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Cube Goodies: Atari Paddle 13-in-1 TV Games - 2 Player]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/cubegoodies/toys/68f7/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Caffeine: Buzz Bites Chocolate Chews]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/caffeine/candy/6e1c/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Computing: Web Developer Laminated Reference Set]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/computing/accessories/6de0/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Tshirts: Rays Cast]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/tshirts/science/6df7/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Tshirts: Schrödinger's Cat]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/tshirts/science/6dff/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Caffeine: Foosh Energy Mints]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/caffeine/candy/6e27/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Cube Goodies: Star Wars Force FX Lightsabers]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/cubegoodies/toys/69de/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Caffeine: Bawls Mints - High Caffeine Candy]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/caffeine/candy/6b77/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[PC Mods: Zalman Reserator Water Cooling System]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/pcmods/cooling/6ea8/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Computing: USB to Bluetoooth Adapter]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/computing/input/6dd0/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[PC Mods: Coolermaster Wavemaster PC Case]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/pcmods/cases/6ed1/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Electronics: Panasonic 5.8GHz Cordless Phone]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/electronics/phones/6e45/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Tshirts: Soylent Green Is People]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/tshirts/generic/6e87/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Tshirts: Pi By Numbers]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/tshirts/science/6e7e/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Computing: Wireless-G to USB 2.0 Flex Adapter]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/computing/accessories/6f2a/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Computing: Quick Cam Orbit]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/computing/accessories/6f33/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845400723</hlid>
      <guid>63230845400723</guid>
      <owner>63230845205222</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Computing: Logitech MX1000 Laser Mouse]]></title>
      <link>http://www.thinkgeek.com/computing/input/6efc/?cpg=wnrdf</link>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:20+01:00</date>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845403948</hlid>
      <guid>63230845403948</guid>
      <owner>63230845224039</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Complex Project Manager 2004-05-03]]></title>
      <link>http://software.freshmeat.net/releases/159552/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A project manager.]]></body>
      <date>2004-05-05T08:52:00+-08</date>
      <image>http://images.freshmeat.net/button.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845403948</hlid>
      <guid>63230845403948</guid>
      <owner>63230845224039</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[sign 1.0.2]]></title>
      <link>http://software.freshmeat.net/releases/159810/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A file signing and signature verification utility.]]></body>
      <date>2004-05-05T09:27:00+-08</date>
      <image>http://images.freshmeat.net/button.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845403948</hlid>
      <guid>63230845403948</guid>
      <owner>63230845224039</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[DeBlog 0.2]]></title>
      <link>http://software.freshmeat.net/releases/159811/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A one-file PHP Weblog.]]></body>
      <date>2004-05-05T09:32:00+-08</date>
      <image>http://images.freshmeat.net/button.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845403948</hlid>
      <guid>63230845403948</guid>
      <owner>63230845224039</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[mnoGoSearch 3.2.17 (3.2.x)]]></title>
      <link>http://software.freshmeat.net/releases/159812/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Fast WWW search engine for your site]]></body>
      <date>2004-05-05T09:33:00+-08</date>
      <image>http://images.freshmeat.net/button.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845403948</hlid>
      <guid>63230845403948</guid>
      <owner>63230845224039</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[H-Sphere 2.4]]></title>
      <link>http://software.freshmeat.net/releases/159722/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Web Hosting Control Panel.]]></body>
      <date>2004-05-05T09:38:00+-08</date>
      <image>http://images.freshmeat.net/button.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845403948</hlid>
      <guid>63230845403948</guid>
      <owner>63230845224039</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Leafnode 1.9.53.rel]]></title>
      <link>http://software.freshmeat.net/releases/159813/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[An NNTP server for small leaf sites.]]></body>
      <date>2004-05-05T09:39:00+-08</date>
      <image>http://images.freshmeat.net/button.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845403948</hlid>
      <guid>63230845403948</guid>
      <owner>63230845224039</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[wmfire 1.2.0]]></title>
      <link>http://software.freshmeat.net/releases/159815/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A fiery dockapp monitor.]]></body>
      <date>2004-05-05T10:27:00+-08</date>
      <image>http://images.freshmeat.net/button.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845403948</hlid>
      <guid>63230845403948</guid>
      <owner>63230845224039</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[phpQLAdmin 2.0.18c]]></title>
      <link>http://software.freshmeat.net/releases/159816/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[An LDAP user administration interface.]]></body>
      <date>2004-05-05T10:28:00+-08</date>
      <image>http://images.freshmeat.net/button.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845403948</hlid>
      <guid>63230845403948</guid>
      <owner>63230845224039</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[GnomeBoy Advance 0.2]]></title>
      <link>http://software.freshmeat.net/releases/159817/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A GNOME 2 frontend for the Visual Boy Advance emulator.]]></body>
      <date>2004-05-05T10:30:00+-08</date>
      <image>http://images.freshmeat.net/button.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845403948</hlid>
      <guid>63230845403948</guid>
      <owner>63230845224039</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[IDX-Tsunami 1.0.beta6]]></title>
      <link>http://software.freshmeat.net/releases/159818/</link>
      <body><![CDATA[A distributed multi-protocol load testing tool.]]></body>
      <date>2004-05-05T10:30:00+-08</date>
      <image>http://images.freshmeat.net/button.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845405770</hlid>
      <guid>63230845405770</guid>
      <owner>63230845234404</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[TeXML: an XML vocabulary for TeX]]></title>
      <link>http://www.xmlhack.com/read.php?item=2182</link>
      <body><![CDATA[TeXML is an XML vocabulary for TeX. The processor transforms TeXML markup into the TeX markup, escaping special and out-of-encoding characters. Intended audience is developers who convert documents from XML to TeX.]]></body>
      <topic>Tools</topic>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:25+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.xmlhack.com/images/mynetscape88.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845405770</hlid>
      <guid>63230845405770</guid>
      <owner>63230845234404</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Editors' Newswire for 16 April, 2004]]></title>
      <link>http://www.xmlhack.com/read.php?item=2183</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Newswire stories, including: XML Processing Model Requirements Note from XML Core Working Group; xml:id Working Draft Published; XInclude goes to Candidate Recommendation.]]></body>
      <topic>Newswire items</topic>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:25+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.xmlhack.com/images/mynetscape88.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845405770</hlid>
      <guid>63230845405770</guid>
      <owner>63230845234404</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Editors' Newswire for 21 April, 2004]]></title>
      <link>http://www.xmlhack.com/read.php?item=2184</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Newswire stories, including: PadML -- Photo Album Description Markup Language.]]></body>
      <topic>Newswire items</topic>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:25+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.xmlhack.com/images/mynetscape88.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845405770</hlid>
      <guid>63230845405770</guid>
      <owner>63230845234404</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Editors' Newswire for 5 May, 2004]]></title>
      <link>http://www.xmlhack.com/read.php?item=2185</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Newswire stories, including: Just a few days left to submit proposals for XML 2004.]]></body>
      <topic>Newswire items</topic>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:25+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.xmlhack.com/images/mynetscape88.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845405780</hlid>
      <guid>63230845405780</guid>
      <owner>63230845234404</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Editors' Newswire for 6 May, 2004]]></title>
      <link>http://www.xmlhack.com/read.php?item=2186</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Newswire stories, including: First International Workshop on High Performance XML Processing.]]></body>
      <topic>Newswire items</topic>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:25+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.xmlhack.com/images/mynetscape88.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845405780</hlid>
      <guid>63230845405780</guid>
      <owner>63230845234404</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[That's all for now]]></title>
      <link>http://www.xmlhack.com/read.php?item=2187</link>
      <body><![CDATA[It's been a lot of fun writing XMLhack since 1999, but it's time for us to take a rest.]]></body>
      <topic>Comment</topic>
      <date>2004-09-14T11:43:25+01:00</date>
      <image>http://www.xmlhack.com/images/mynetscape88.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845410958</hlid>
      <guid>http://news.com.com/Nokia%27s+take+on+%2720s+glamour/2009-1041_3-5360187.html?part=rss&amp;tag=5360187&amp;subj=news.1041.5</guid>
      <owner>63230845381365</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Nokia's take on '20s glamour]]></title>
      <link>http://news.com.com/Nokia%27s+take+on+%2720s+glamour/2009-1041_3-5360187.html?part=rss&amp;tag=5360187&amp;subj=news.1041.5</link>
      <body><![CDATA[New models from the Finnish phone giant are designed to recall 'old world' style.]]></body>
      <topic>Personal Technology</topic>
      <date>2004-09-09T14:06:00+-7</date>
      <image>http://i.i.com.com/cnwk.1d/i/ne/gr/prtnr/rss_logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845410958</hlid>
      <guid>http://news.com.com/A+new+handshake+for+mini+hard+drives%3F/2100-1041_3-5360309.html?part=rss&amp;tag=5360309&amp;subj=news.1041.5</guid>
      <owner>63230845381365</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[A new handshake for mini hard drives?]]></title>
      <link>http://news.com.com/A+new+handshake+for+mini+hard+drives%3F/2100-1041_3-5360309.html?part=rss&amp;tag=5360309&amp;subj=news.1041.5</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Intel, Hitachi, Toshiba and others propose CE-ATA, a new interface for miniature hard drives used in consumer electronics.]]></body>
      <topic>Personal Technology</topic>
      <date>2004-09-09T15:14:00+-7</date>
      <image>http://i.i.com.com/cnwk.1d/i/ne/gr/prtnr/rss_logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845410958</hlid>
      <guid>http://news.com.com/Qualcomm+pays+%24170+million+for+display+start-up/2100-1047_3-5360606.html?part=rss&amp;tag=5360606&amp;subj=news.1047.5</guid>
      <owner>63230845381365</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[Qualcomm pays $170 million for display start-up]]></title>
      <link>http://news.com.com/Qualcomm+pays+%24170+million+for+display+start-up/2100-1047_3-5360606.html?part=rss&amp;tag=5360606&amp;subj=news.1047.5</link>
      <body><![CDATA[The wireless company buys a majority stake in Iridigm, developer of a brighter, low-cost alternative to LCD screens.]]></body>
      <topic>Personal Technology</topic>
      <date>2004-09-09T17:45:00+-7</date>
      <image>http://i.i.com.com/cnwk.1d/i/ne/gr/prtnr/rss_logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845410958</hlid>
      <guid>http://news.com.com/The+Woz+has+got+game/2110-1043_3-5360644.html?part=rss&amp;tag=5360644&amp;subj=news.1043.5</guid>
      <owner>63230845381365</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[The Woz has got game]]></title>
      <link>http://news.com.com/The+Woz+has+got+game/2110-1043_3-5360644.html?part=rss&amp;tag=5360644&amp;subj=news.1043.5</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Apple Computer co-founder Steve Wozniak joins advisory board of start-up Eye Games.]]></body>
      <topic>Personal Technology</topic>
      <date>2004-09-09T18:37:00+-7</date>
      <image>http://i.i.com.com/cnwk.1d/i/ne/gr/prtnr/rss_logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item>
   <item>
      <hlid>63230845410958</hlid>
      <guid>http://news.com.com/After+loud+lows%2C+Gateway+hopes+to+moove+into+black/2100-1041_3-5363992.html?part=rss&amp;tag=5363992&amp;subj=news.1041.5</guid>
      <owner>63230845381365</owner>
      <title><![CDATA[After loud lows, Gateway hopes to moove into black]]></title>
      <link>http://news.com.com/After+loud+lows%2C+Gateway+hopes+to+moove+into+black/2100-1041_3-5363992.html?part=rss&amp;tag=5363992&amp;subj=news.1041.5</link>
      <body><![CDATA[Not to be cowed by string of losses, PC maker enacts sweeping changes designed to quickly return it to profitability.]]></body>
      <topic>Personal Technology</topic>
      <date>2004-09-13T11:55:00+-7</date>
      <image>http://i.i.com.com/cnwk.1d/i/ne/gr/prtnr/rss_logo.gif</image>
      <read>0</read>
   </item></headlines>